Chihiro... Chihiro!
We're almost there.
いななか
やっぱり田舎ねぇ
We'll have to drive into town just to go shopping.
It'll be Home Sweet Home in no time.
Look, there's the elementary.
Chihiro, that's your new school.
What a charming little place.
I wanna go back to my old school...
Mom, my flowers are all squished!
What did you expect?
You've been clutching them since we left.
We'll put them in water when we get to the house.
初めてもらっだ花束が
お別れの花束なんて悲しい
What are you talking about?
You got a rose for your birthday, didn't you?
Yeah, one.
One's hardly a bouquet.
You dropped the card. I'm opening the window.
Be good today,
we've got a lot to do.
SPIRITED AWAY
For my Sisters. Happy birthday!
Translation by Colin W
Huh? Did I miss the turnoff?
I could have sworn...
Isn't that it up there?
That green house on the end, right?
That's the one.
I must have turned too early.
Maybe I can swing around somewhere up here...
Oh not again,
we get lost every time you say that.
Let's just take a look.
What are those little houses?
The stone shrines? Spirits live in them.
Dad, is this really the right way?
No problem sweetie,
this car's a four-wheel drive.
Chihiro, put your seatbelt on.
Honey, you're going to get us killed!
A tunnel!
Where are we?
Looks like a gate or something.
Let's just get out of here! Honey!
Chihiro!
You two...
Mortar walls?
This place can't be that old.
The wind's being sucked in...
What is all this?
Wanna take a peek?
Looks like we can walk through.
This place gives me the creeps,
let's get out of here!
Come on scardy-pants,
you'll be fine.
Just a bit, I promise.
The movers will beat us to the house at this rate...
Don't sweat it, they've got the keys.
They know what to do.
I guess so...
No! I'm not going in there!
Dad, let's get out of here!
Come on, it'll be fine.
I'm not going!
Just wait in the car then,
we'll be back in a minute.
Mom!
Don't leave me!
Watch your step.
Chihiro, stop tugging my arm,
I can't walk straight.
Where are we?
Hear that?
It's a train!
We might be near a station.
Come on, we'll find out soon enough!
What are houses doing here?
Just as I thought.
This is some run-down amusement park.
They built tons of these back in the 90s.
Then the bubble burst and they all went belly-up.
This has got to be one of those.
えー まだが行くの
Dad, let's go home already!
Hey!
Mom, that building's howling at us!
It's just the wind.
What a nice place!
I should have brought the sandwiches
from the car.
They even tried to put in a river.
Smell that?
I smell barbeque.
You're right.
This place might still be operating.
Chihiro, hurry up.
Wait!
Over here.
How disappointing...
it's all just restaurants.
I don't see anybody...
There!
In here.
Look at all this!
'Scuse me, anyone around?
Come sit Chihiro,
the food looks wonderful.
Anyone back there?
Let's just start.
They'll be by soon;
we can pay them then.
Good point.
Oh man, look at these...
I wonder what kind of bird this is.
It's fantastic!
Chihiro, you have to try this.
I don't want any!
Let's get out of here...
We're going to get in trouble.
Don't worry kiddo,
your dad'll handle it.
I've got cash on me,
what could they be mad about?
Come try this, already!
The meat is to die for.
Sauce.
Thanks.
Mom! Dad!
That's weird...
A train!
You cannot be here!
You must leave!
The sun is setting! You have to hurry!
The lamps... Run!
I'll buy you some time.
Get back across the river!
What's with him?
Dad!
Dad, we gotta go!
We have to hurry!
Dad!
Mom!
Water?
No way...
I'm dreaming!
This isn't real!
Wake up! This isn't real!
Please...
Just a dream... just a dream...
Not real... none of it's real...
Wake up...
I'm see-through!
Wake up, wake up, wake up!
Don't be afraid, I'm a friend.
No! No! No!
Eat this, hurry.
If you don't eat some of our food,
you're going to disappear completely.
No!
Trust me.
You won't turn into a pig.
Chew it and swallow.
Good girl. You're safe now.
See for yourself.
It worked...
See? Now it's time to go.
Where are my mom and dad?
They didn't really turn into pigs, did they?
We can't help them right now,
but I promise you'll see them soon.
Quiet.
They're looking for you.
We're out of time.
We'll run for it!
I can't stand up!
My legs won't budge.
Relax and take a deep breath.
In the name of the Wind and Water within you...
Release!
Now stand!
You can't breathe while we're crossing the bridge.
If you take even one breath,
the spell will break and you'll be seen.
I'm scared.
Relax.
Good evening! Welcome!
Welcome, welcome!
I have returned from my duties!
Welcome back, sir!
Breathe deep.
Hold it!
Welcome!
We've been waiting for you!
Just a bit further.
Lord Haku!
Where were you last night?
A human?
Run!
Haku! Lord Haku!
Smell that? There's a human sneaking about!
What a stench.
They know you're close.
I'm sorry... He surprised me...
You did well, Chihiro.
Listen to me carefully now.
If you stay here, they'll find you.
I'm going to head inside and
lead them away from you.
You have to escape while I have them confused.
No! Don't leave me!
Stay here with me, please!
You don't understand.
There's no other way for you to survive in this place.
Don't you want to rescue your parents?
So... they really did turn into pigs...
Stay still.
When things calm down,
head out the little door in the back.
Take the stairs all the way to the bottom.
That's where the boiler room is.
It's where they heat water for the baths.
You'll find Old Kama inside.
You must reach him.
Old Kama?
You're going to ask him for a job.
He'll turn you down, but don't give up.
It's the rule of this place;
Yubaba turns those who won't work into animals.
Yubaba?
You'll know her when you see her.
She's the witch who runs this place.
But you must not complain.
She'll make you want to quit,
but don't give in to her.
You'll get your chance for freedom,
just be patient.
Do that, and there's nothing she can do to you.
Okay...
Haku! Lord Haku!
It's time.
Remember, Chihiro. I'll always be on your side.
How do you know my name?
I've known you for a long time.
My name is Haku.
I'm here!
Sir, the Mistress is calling for you!
I'm aware. What do you think I've been doing?
Um...
Excuse me...
I, uh...
Are you Old Kama?
I... Haku told me to come here
and ask you for a job!
This many?
Break's over, people!
Yeah I'm Ol' Kama...
Just an old bag o' bones that boils the water.
You little runts, get out here already!
Um, well, please let me work here!
I've got all the help I need.
There's soot all over this place.
Lots of backup if I need it!
Ah, sorry...
Give me a second.
Out of the way.
Now what?
Can I just leave it here?
If you're going to help, then help, dammit!
You little slackers!
Want me to turn you back into dust?
And you! Butting in where you don't belong
and stealing people's work!
Listen, kid. If these little motes don't work,
the magic binding them wears off
and they fall apart.
There's no work here for you.
Go beg somewhere else!
Ingrates! You got a problem?
Get back to work this instant!
Grub's up!
At it again, I see.
And where's yesterday's bowl?
You know I told you to leave it by the door!
Meal break! Come and get it!
Holy crap, a human!
They're freaking out upstairs over her!
She's my grand-daughter.
You have a...?
Says she wants a job
but there's no room for her down here.
Do me a favour.
Take her to Yubaba and get her sorted out.
あとは自分でやるだろう
Like hell I will! Yubaba will take my head off!
I'll sweeten the deal.
Charred Imori... a delicacy.
Either way, if she wants a job
she has to sign a contract with Yubaba.
It's up to fate now, kiddo.
Alright brat, let's go.
あんだね
ハイとか お世話じなりますとか
言えないの?
あかハイ
ドンくさいね 早くおいで
Yes!
The hell you need shoes for?
Leave the socks too!
Okay!
You forgot to thank Old Kama!
He's really sticking his neck out for you!
Thank you very much.
Good luck.
Yubaba's office is at the back of the top floor.
Come on!
You lose your nose doing that.
There's another elevator after this.
Okay.
We're there.
Welcome, sir!
My apologies, sir.
This elevator doesn't go any higher.
There should be another nearby.
He's following us...
Keep your eyes to yourself.
And we've arrived!
Yours is the first parlor on the right.
Rin!
Yes sir!
Don't you smell that?
Human! You reek like a human!
How could that be?
Oh no, I smell it. Something tasty...
What are you hiding?
Fess up! What've you got?
You got me... it's this.
A blackchar...
Give it!
No way!
The sisters had me pick this up special.
I'm begging you, just a little bite!
Sir, just pull the lever
to reach the higher floors!
Ever heard of knocking?
まあ
Well, come in.
Now, kid!
Oww...
Pipe down, I'm writing.
Um...
Please let me work here.
That's the dumbest thing I've heard all week.
What use would you be? You're all skin and bones.
This is nowhere for a human to be.
Every God and spirit in the land comes here
to rest their weary soul.
And don't get me started about your parents!
Gorging themselves on food for my customers.
No better than pigs!
They got what they deserved.
And you.
You're never going home.
Might as well turn you into a piglet.
Or perhaps a lump of coal?
You're trembling.
I should congratulate you for making it this far.
You must have had some help...
...and that person deserves a reward, don't you think?
Tell me who it was.
I want to work here!
I said no!
Please give me a job!
Never...!
Why on earth
do I have to give you of all people a job?
Look at you! A spoiled, lazy, cry-baby!
You think there's work around here
for a stupid little brat like you?
No means no!
One more slacker under this roof
and I'll go out of business!
Or maybe...
...maybe I'll stick you in the worst place I can find
and watch you work yourself to death?
Oh no, oh my...
Be good sweetie, I'll be right there...
What are you still doing there? Leave already!
I said I want a job!
Keep your voice down!
Oh sweetums, don't be like that...
What a perfect little baby...
Give! Me! A! Job!
Fine! Fine! Just be quiet!
Ahh there there...
Your contract.
Sign the dotted line.
You're hired.
But if I hear even one complaint
one whimper out of you
you'll be eating slop out of a bucket like your parents!
I sign it here?
Yes, and hurry it up!
I don't have all night.
I was a fool.
I never should have sworn that oath...
...to hand out a job to any passerby who wants one!
Done yet?
Yes...
Your name is Chihiro?
Yes, ma'am.
That's too good a name for you.
From this moment forward your name is Sen.
Got it, Sen?
Answer me when I call your name!
Yes, ma'am!
You summoned me?
This kid's our newest hire. Get her fixed up with the girls.
Understood.
What is your name?
My name is Sen.
This way, Sen.
Haku... I...
Who said you could speak?
And you will refer to me as Lord Haku.
The mistress's order it may be...
...but a human, here?
Out of the question.
She has signed a contract.
You're kidding.
I promise to do my best.
I hope they don't send her our way...
She reeks that human stench!
Give her three days with our food
and her smell will clear.
If she's still of no use to you
then fry her or boil her, it's up to you.
Now back to work!
Where is Rin?
What? You're sticking her with me?
You wanted an understudy.
Oh, Rin is just perfect for this.
Go, Sen.
Okay!
I don't believe this!
You guys owe me one.
Get going.
Come on!
Kid, you did it!
You're a bit of a wimp, so I was worried.
Stay sharp around here.
You come to me if you've got a problem, okay?
What's wrong?
My legs won't stop shaking.
This is where we sleep.
Dinner and a good night's sleep and you'll feel better.
Here's your smock. Gotta wash it yourself.
Leggings.
Is any of this going to fit you...?
Too big.
Rin-san?
Yeah?
Are there... two people named Haku here?
Two of 'em?
One is quite enough, thank you very much.
Still too big.
He's Yubaba's right-hand-man, can't trust the guy.
Watch yourself around him.
There's gotta be one in here...
Finally found one!
Hey, what's the matter now?
Hang in there, kid.
Will you two keep it down?
The new girl's not feeling good.
Meet me at the bridge.
I'll take you to your parents.
Where are my shoes?
Thanks.
This way.
Dad! Mom! It's me!
It's me, Sen!
Mom! Dad!
Are they okay? Are they sick?
They're fine, just sleeping off all the food.
Right now they don't even know they were human.
Dad, Mom,
I'm going to get you out of here!
あんまり太っちゃだめだよ
食べられちゃうからね
Hide these somewhere safe.
I thought they threw them out.
You'll need them when you leave this place.
The card I got at my farewell party...
Chihiro?
Chihiro... that's my name!
Yubaba controls others by seizing their true names.
You'll be Sen on the surface
with your true name spirited away within your heart.
She almost had me.
I was almost Sen for real.
If you lose your name
you'll never find your way back home.
I... have forgotten mine.
Your real name?
But it's strange, I remember you so clearly.
Here. You haven't eaten yet, right?
I'm not hungry.
千尋の元気が出るように
まじないをがけて作っだんだ お食べ
つらかっだたろう さっ お食べ
ひとりで戻れるね
うん ハクありがとう 私がんばるね
うん
ああ...
ん...
ん?
どこへ行ってだんだよ 心配してだんだぞ
ごめんなさい
じゃまだねえ
うわっ
のゝ
ツ
ウッ・
ちから
千 もっとカカ 入んないの?
おおゆばん
リンと千 今日から大湯番だ
あれはカエルの仕事だろう
うわやくぐく ほねみ
上役の命令だ 骨身をおしおなみよ
あの... そこ添れませんか?
千 早くしろよ
バーイ
ここ あけときますね
リン 大湯だって?
ほっとけ
ひでえ ずーっと洗ってないぞ これ
クックックッ
わっ/
ワッパWVV
このフロはさ 拓れだお名専門んだよ
こびりついてて取れやしない
リン 千 一番客が来ちおまうぞ
バーイ 今すぐ...
チェッ 見えすいだイビリしやがって
ー回 くすり湯人入れなきゃだめだ
ばんだい 必だ
千 番台へ行って札をもらって来な
Aふだ?
ワッ/
くすみり湯の札だよ
バーイ
リンさん 番台ってなに?
うん?
なんだろうね なんガ来だね
雨とまぎれて
ログでもないものがまぎれこんだがな
そんなもっだいないことができるが
おはようございます/
よくお休みになられましだな
かがさま
いおう じょう
ハイ 硫黄の上
いつまでいたって同じだ 戻れ 戻れ
手でこすればいいんだ
おはようございます
手を使え 手を
でも... あの...
くすみり湯じゃないと だめだそうです
わからんやつだな
あっ よもぎ湯ですね
どうぞ ごゆっくの...
あっ/
ハイ 番台です
あっ ハイ... ワァッ/
あっ/ ありがとうございます/
ああ 違う
こら 待て おい
どうんるんを人2
いえ なんでもありません
なにか入りこんでいるよ
ス乱6のみみ2
それを調べるんだ
今日は ハフワがいないからね
ヘスえー ずい分いいのくれだじゃん
これがさ カマジイのとこへへ行くんだ
混んでないからすぐ来るよ きっと
これを引けばお湯が出る やってみな
わっ/
千って ほんとドジな
わーっ すごい色
ひもの
こいつにはさミミズの千物が入ってんだ
こんだけ濁ってり や
こすらなくても同じだな
いっぱいになっだら もう一回引きな
止まるがら
もう 放して大丈夫だよ
オレ 朝めし取ってくんな
バーイ
あ...
ワッ
いだい
あの... おフロまだなんです
こんなにだくさん...
ウ... の... の...
え... 私にじくれるの?
ア... ア...
あの... それ... そんなにいらない
ア...
だめよ ひとつでいいの
アッ/
ああ/
奥さま/
がみ
クサレ神だって?
それも特大のオクサレさまです
まっすぐ橋へ向かって来ます
お帰り下さい お引きとの下さい
お帰り下さい
グ... サ... イ...
ウーン おかしいね
クサレ神の気配なんかじ ゃなかっだんだが
来ちおまっだものは仕方がない お和えしな/
こうなっだら できるだけ早く
引きとってもらうしかガないよ
オクサレさまです お早く お早く
リンと千 湯パーパさまがお呼びだ
ハバパ... バイ/
いいかい お前の初仕事だ
これから来るお客を大湯で世話するんだよ
あ あの...
四の五の言うと 石炭としちまうよ
わかっだね/
み みえましただ/
ウッ/
おやめ お客さんに失礼だよ
ヨク オコヒクダサヒマヒタダ...
ア... オカネ...
セン セン... ハヤクオウケトリナ
ハハバイ
ウーッ/
ナニヒテルンダイ
ハヤクゴアンナイヒナ/
ド ドウゾ
ウ...!
セーン/
ウー ひでえ...
めしが/
窓をおあけ 全部だよ
ヴー
え? ちょっと待って
きだな
ホホホホホホ 汚いね
笑いごとではありません
あのどうするかがね
ホオ だし湯をする気だよ
ああ 渦い手で避に節りおって
フン/
ウワッ/
アー/
ん? 千に新しい札 あげちのかい?
まさか そんなもっだいない
ウ...!
アッ/
ああ あんな高価なくすりの湯を
あ...!
セーツン / 千どこだ/
リンさん/
大丈夫ガ?
カマジイにありっだけのお湯 出すように
頼んできだ
最高のくすり湯をおごってくれるって/
ありがとう
あの ここにトゲみだいのがささってるの
トゲ?
深くてとれないの/
トゲ? トゲだって?
ウーン 下に人数を集めな
ヘッタツ
急ぎな
千とリン
そのお方はおクサレ神ではないぞ
このロープをお使い
ハイ
よっと
しっなかり持ってろ
ハイ
グズグズするんじゃないよ
女も力を合わせるんだ
結びました
ゃ
んー/ 難- 心をそろえて
ひけやー それッ/
そおーれっ
あ/
自転車?
やはり/
さあ引くんだよ
そーれ
ワァー/
アー
うわっ/
セーン 大丈夫か/
よきがな
はっ...
ん... ムムッ/
さきん
砂金だ/
こらーーっ 会社のものだ 勝手にとるな
静かにおし
お客さまがまだおいでなんだよ
千 お客$まのじゃまだ そこをおりな
おおど
大戸をあけな お帰りだ
アッパWVVV
ヤンヤー
おおもう
千 よくやっただね 大儲けだよ
ありゃ 名のある河の主だよ
みんなも千を見習いな
今日はーネつけるかがからね
さあ 拾っだ砂金を全部出しな
そりゃ ひでえや
ケチー
食う? かっぱらって来だ
ありがとう
ャヤレヤレ
ハク いなかっだね
まだハクかがよ
あいつ時々いなくなるんだよ
うわさ
噂じゃさ 湯パバーパに
やばぱいことやらされてんだって
そう...
リン 消すよ
ああ
町がある 海みちい...
当たり前じゃん
雨が疾りゃ海ぐらいできるよ
オレ いつかあの町に行くんだ
こんなとこ 絶対じやめてやる...
ウッ... ムム ム...
どうしただん?
ン/
砂金だ/
あっ/
おま 何者だ / 客人ではないな
そこに入ってはいけないのだぞ
おっ お...
きん
金だ金だ
こ これ わしにくれるのか?
アー... ア... ア...
キ... 金を出せはるのかガ?
ア... ア...
くれ/
誰ぞ そこにおるのか?
しょうとうじかん
消む時間は とうに過ぎだぞ
あにやく
兄役どの オレは腹がへっだ
ハラベコだ
そ その声は?
前金だ とれ
わしは才だぞ フロにも入るぞ
みんな起こごせ
お父さん お母さん
河の神さまからもらっだおダンゴだよ
これを食べれば人間に戻れるよ きっと
お父さん お母さん どこ?
お父さーん
ハバッ/
やな葛
リン?
誰もいない
ああ 本当に海じなってる
ここごから お父さんだちんとこ 見えるんだ
カマジイがもう火をだいてる
そんなに寝ちゃっだのかな
お客さまがお待ちだぞ
もっと早くできんのか そこ/
余り物でもなんでもいい
どんどんお出ししろ
セーン/
リンさん
今 起こしに行こうと思っだんだ 見な/
物の金だ もらっだんだ
すげえ気前のいい客が来たんだ
こちらへ こちらへ 今ひとまき
オレは腹ぺコだ 全部持ってこい
そのお客さんて...
千も来い
湯パーパバ まだ寝てるからチャンスだぞ
私 カマジイんとごこへ 行かなきゃ
今 カマジイのとこ 行かない方がいいぞ
ぷぷきげん
だだき起こされて ものすごく不機嫌だから
リン もう一回行こう
ああ
お父さんとお母さん
わかがからなかっだらどうしよう
お父さんあんまり太ってだらやだなぁ...
ん?
あっ/
橋のとこで見だ意だ
こっちへ来る/
なんだろう 鳥じゃない
キャッ
ハクグー しっかりーっ/
こっちよー
ハク?
ハクー/
ヒャーツッ/
うわあ... あー あー
あ... だだの紙だ...
ハクね? ハグでしょう?
けがしてるの?
あの紙のトリは行ってしまっだよ
もう大丈夫だよ
キャッ/
湯バパーパのとこへ行くんだ...
どうしょう/ ハクが多んじゃう/
そーれ
ノさあてぐもごの奴?きか寺72②
世どん
ノみえさぶのかみなクをひよ そカ
いらっしゃいませー
ノそアカ みねだどク あっ みがカク そカっ/
お大尽さま/ お大尽さま/
来るよ
今度こそもらわなきゃ
わ
いくらでもから湧くべんだって
お大尽さま- こちらへもひとまき一
こらっ なにをする
上へ行くんです
ダメダ ダメダ ん?
わっ 血だ/
あ...
どけどけ お客さまのお通りだ
あの時はありがとうございます
なにをしてる はよ... ウッ
あ...
アー... ア... ア...
エエ... エエ...
欲しくない いらない
私 忙しいので失礼します
ワーッ/
ええい 静まれ 静まらんか/
下がれ 下がれ
れい
これは とんだご無礼をいだしましだ
しんまい こおおすめ
なにぶん新米の人間の小娘でございまして
お前 なぜ笑う
あ?
笑っだな
めっそうもない アアッ/
キャー
食っだー/
ワッ/
ワッ ワッ ワッ ワッ
ハァ バァ ハア...
あ...
湯パーバ
オイ...
ワァッ/
まっだく なんてことだろうね
しょうだい
そいつの正体はカオナシだよ
そう カオナシ/
さくぐ
欲とじかなられて とんでもない客を
引き入れだもんだみよ
あだただしが行くまで
余計なことをすんじゃないよ
しきもの
あーあ 敷物を汚しちまって
お前だち ハクを片づけな
えっ/
もう そのばは使い物とならないよ
あっ/
パア
ンンツン...
ぼう ね
もう 坊はまだベッドで寝ないで...
アアア... アアア...
ああ ごめん ごめん
いいでおネンネしてだのにね
パーパはまだお仕事があるの
ブチュ
いいでおネンネしててね
あっ
ウッー 痛い 放して/
あ... 助けてくれてありがとう
私 急いで行かみななくちゃならないの
放してくれる?
おまえ病気うつしに求だんだな
え?
おんもには悪いパイキンしかいないんだぞ
私 人間よ この世界じゃ
ず
ちょ っと珍しいかもしれないけど
おんもは からだに悪いんだぞ
ここにいて坊とお遊びしろ
あなだた病気なの?
おんもに行くと
病気なるから ここにいるんだ
こんなとこにいただた方が病気になるよ/
あのね
私のとても大切な人が大ケがしてるの
だからすぐ行かみなきゃならないの
お願い 手を放して
行っだら泣いちゃうぞ
坊が泣いたらすぐパーパが拉て
お前なんガ殺しちゃうぞ
ごこんな手すぐ折っちゃうぞ
閣い 痛い/
ね あとで戻って来て遊んであげるから
だめ 今 遊ぶの
ん?
血/ わかる? 自/
フギャー
ギャア ギャア
オイ/
ハクーッ/
なにするの あっち行って シッシッ
ハク/ ハクね しっかのして
静かにして / ハク/
ギャー
ギャア ギャア
あっち行って
あっ ダメーッ
血なんがガ平気だぞ
遊ばないと泣いちゃうぞ
待って ね いいだから
坊と遊ばないと泣いちゃうぞ
お願い 待って/
うるさいねぇ
静かにしておくれ
あんだはちょっと太りすぎね
す
やっぱりちょっと透けるわねぇ
バーバ
やれやれ
お母さんと あだしの区別もつかないのかい
その万が少しは動きやすいだろう
さて... と_ お前だちちはなにがいいかね
フフフ...
ないしょ
このごことは内緒だよ
に3
誰かにしゃべると お前の口が裂けるからね
あなだは誰?
ふだご
湯バパーパの双子の姉さ
お前さんのおかげで
ここを見物できて面白かっだよ
わだ
さあ その和竜を渡しな
ハクをどうするの? ひどいケガなの
そいつは妹の手先のドロボー竜だよ
私の所から大事な/ ンコをみ出した
ハクがそんなことしっこない/
優しい人だもん
竜はみんな優しいよ
優しくておろかだ
魔法の力を才に入れようとして
の弟子になるなんてね
よくぐぷか
この若者は欲深の妹の言いなりだ
さあ そこをどきな
どのみち この息はもう助からないよ
ハンコには守りのまじないが
がかけてあるからね
盗んだ者が死ぬようにと
イヤッ だめッ
なんだろうね この連中は
コレッ おやめ 部屋じお戻りな
シャーツ
ああっ/
あらあら 漠断しだねえ
ハクーッ あっ だめ キャアーッ
ハクーッ
オオ... ワッ/
なにごとじゃい/
ああ... 待ちなさい
ハク/
苦しいの?
このりゃ いかん
ハク しっかり/
どうしょう ハクが持んじゃう
かガらだの中で なにかがガ千命を食い荒らしとる
カラダの中?
強い魔法な わしじはどうにもならん
ハク これ河の神さまがくれだおダンゴ
効くかもしれない 食べて
ハク 口をあけて /
ハク お願い 食べて
ほら 平気だよ
そりゃあこガダンゴガ?
あけて いい了だガから...
大丸夫 飲みこんで/
出ち / こいつだ
あっ/
ハンコ/
六げた/ あっち/ あっち/ あっち/
ウワッ あっ あっ
キィキィキイィ...
アアーッ ワッ ワッ ワッ...
エンがチョ キキ/ エンがチョ
きっだた/
おじさん これ
湯バパーパのお姉さんのハンコなの
けいやぐいん
ゼーニーパの? 魔女の契約印ひ/
そりゃ まだ えらいものを...
ああ... やっぱりハクだ
おじさん ハクよ
オウ オウ
ハク/ バク/ パク/
おじさん/ ハク 息してない
まだしとるがな
魔法の傷は油断できんが...
これで少しは落ち着くといいんだが...
ハクはな
とつぜん
千と同じように 突然ここにやって来てな
魔法使いじなりだいと言いおってな
わしは反対しだんだ
魔女の弟子なんぞ ロワなことはないってな
聞かないんだみよ
もう帰る所はないと
とうとう 湯パーパの弟子じなっちまっだ
そのうち どんどん顔色は悪くなるし
目つきばかりきつくなってな
カマジイさん 私 これ
湯バパーパのお姉さんに返してくる
返して 謝って
ハクを助けてくれるように頼んでみる
お姉さんのいる所を教えて
ゼニーパの所へか?
あの魔女はコエエぞ
お願い
ハクは 私を助けてくれだの
私 ハフを助けちい
うーん 行くにじはなぁ
行けるだろうが 帰りがなぁ...
待ちなさい
だしガか... と ここだっだかが...
みんな 私のクツと服 お願いね
千/ すしん揚しだんだぞ
ん?
リンさん
ハクじゃん なんかあっだのか ここ?
なんだ そいつら
新しい友達なの ねっ
湯バパーパがカンカンになって
お前のこと捜してるぞ
気前がいいと思ってだ客が
ばけもん
カオナシって化物だっだんだよ
湯バパーパは千が引き入れだって言うんだ
あ そうかもしれない
エエッ ほんとかよ
だってお客さんだと思っだから...
どうすんだみよ
あいつ もう三人も飲んじゃっだんだぞ
あっだ これだ/ 千 あっだぞ
じいさん 今 忙しいんだよ
これが使える
電車のキップじゃん
どこで手に入れだの こんなの
40年前の使い残りだ
いいか 電車で6つ目の
ぬま
「沼の底」 という駅だ
沼の底?
そうだ とにかく6フつ目だ
6つ目ね
間違えるなよ
昔は 戻りの電車があっだんだが
近ごろは行きっぱなしだ
それでも行くかだ
せんろ
うん 帰りは線路を歩いて来るからいい
湯バパーパはどうするんだよ
ごこれから行く
ハク きっと戻って来るガから
死んじゃだめだよ
なにがどうしたの?
わかがからんがか 艇だ 愛
ヒヤーッ
ますます9大きくなってるよ
ヤダ
あだい食われただくない
来だよ
千か よかっだた
湯パバーパさまでは もう 押えられんのだ
オホホホホホ...
なにもそんなに暴れなくても
千は来ますよ
千はどこだ 千を出せ
さっ 急げ
湯パーパさま 千です
遅い/
お客さま 千が来ましだよ
ほんのちょっと お待ち下さいね
ウーッ/
なにをグズグズしてだんだい/
おおぞん
このままじゃ大損だ/
あいつをおだてて
しぼれるだけ金をしぼり出させ...
う...?
チュウ
きだな
なんだい その汚いネズミは
えっ?
あの... ご存じないですガ?
知るわけないだろう おー いやだ
さぁ 行きな
ごゆっくり
千ひとりで大丈夫でしょうか
お前が代わるかい
ヒ...!
フン
これ食うか うまいぞー
きん
金を出そうがか...
千の他には
出してやらないことにしだんだ
こっちへおいで
千はなにが欲しいんだ 言ってごらん
あなだはどこから来の?
私すぐ行かみななきゃならないとこがあるの
ううっ
あなだは来だ所へ帰っだ万がいいよ
私が欲しいものは
ぜっだい
あなだには絶対出はない
うち
お家はどこなの?
お父さんやお母さん いるんでしょう?
イヤダ... イヤダ...
さみしい さみしい...
お家がわからないの?
千ほしい 千ほしい-
欲しがれ
私を食べる気?
取れっ
取れ/
チュッ/パ
私を食べるなら その前にこれを食べて
ほんとは お父さんとお母さんに
あげだかっただんだけど あげるね
ウウウ... アアアアア
オ... グエー
センー
小如がなにを食わし... グェー
みんな おどき/
お客さまとて許せぬ/
アウッ...
こっちだよー
こっち/
許せん/
セーツン / こっちだぁ
来ち/ こっちだよー/
呼んでどうすんだよ
ア... アア... ア・...
ゅ やゃ
あの人 湯屋にいるからいけないの
あそこなを出だ方がいいんだよ
だって どこ連れてくんだよ
わガんないけど...
わがんないって...
あーあ ついて来るぞ あいつ
ウー ゲホッ
ん?
ここごがかがら歩け
うん
駅は行けばわかるって
ありがとう
必ず戻って求いよ/
うん/
セーン/
お前のこと ドンくさいって言っだけど
取り消すぞ一
カオナシー
千じなにかしだら 許さないガからな/
あれだ
電車が来
来るよ
あの 沼の底までお願いします
えっ?
あなだも乗りちいの?
ア... ア...
あの この人もお願いします
おいで
おとなしくしててね
おじいさん
ん... うーん...
お... ハク 気がついだか
おじいさん 千はどこです
なにがあっだのでしょう 教えて下さい
お前 なにも覚えてないのか
きれぎれにしかガ思い出せはません
間の中で千尋が回民も私を車びました
その声を頼りじにもがしいて 気がついただら
ここに寝ていましだた
そうか 千尋か
あのは千尋というのなか
いいなぁ 愛の力だな
きん
これっぱかしの金で
どう埋め合わせするのさ
千のバカが
せっかくの骨けをフイにしちまって...
で でも
千のおガげでオレだたち助かっだんです
おだまり /
みんな自分でまいだ種じゃないか
それなのに勝手に逃げ出しだんだよ
あの了は自分の親を見捨てだんだ/
親豚は食べごどろだろ
ベーコンにでもハムにでもしちまいな
お待ち下さい
ハクさま/
なんだい お前 生きてだのかがい
まだ わかりませんか
大切なものがす の替わっ だのに
なまいき
ずいぷん生意気な口をきくね
いつガからそんなにエラくなっだんだい
オイ/
オイ オイ オイ オイ...
坊...
ああ/
キャー
坊一/
土くれだ/
どこにいるの 上坊/
出て来ておくれ
坊/
坊 坊
おのれー
言えー
あだしの坊をどこへやっだぁ
ゼーニーパの所です
ゼニーバ?
ああ...
しょうわる
なるほどね 性悪女め
それであたしに勝ったつもりかい
ヒヒヒビヒ...
で どうするんだい
坊を連れ戻して来ます
その代わり千と両親を
人間の世界へ戻してやって下さい
それでお前はどうなるんだい
ざ
そのあと 税に八殖きじされてもいいんかい/
この駅でいいんだよね...
行こう
ハァハァバァバァアー
かだ
肩にのっていいよ
ん?
あ...
お入り
失礼します
入るならサッサとお入り
おいで
みんなよくぐ来ね
あ あの
まぁ お座り
今 お茶をいれるからね
ゼニーパさん これハクが盗んだものです
お返しに来ました
お前 これがなんだかが知ってるかい
いえ でもとっても大事なものだって...
ハクの代わりに謝りに来ましだ
ごめんなさい
お前これを持っててなんともなかっだかがかい?
えス...?
あれ? 守りのまじないが消えてるねぇ
すいません
あのハンコについてだ変な貝
あだしが臣みつぶしちゃいましだ
踏みつぶしだぁ? アVVVW
あんだ その由はね
あやつ.
妹が弟了を操るだめに
竜の腹じしのぴこませだ中だよ
踏みつぶしだ/ WVVVW
さっ お座り
お前はカオナシだね お前もお座りな
あ あの...
この人だちを元に戻してあげて下さい
おや あんだだち
魔法はとっくに切れてるだろう
戻りだかっだら戻りな
ハァ バァ ハア...
あだしだち二人で一人前なのに
気が合わなくてね
ほら あの人 ハイカラじゃないじゃない
魔女の双子なんて厄介の元ね
お前を助けてあげだいけど
あたしにはどうすることもできないよ
この世界の決まりおだからね
両親のことも
ボーイフレンドの和竜のことも
自分ぐやるしかない
でも あの ヒントかなにかもらえませんガが?
ハクと私 ずっと前に会っちことが
あるみだいなんです
じゃ 話が早いよ
一度あっだことは忘れがないものさ
思い出せはないだけで
まあ 今夜は遅いから ゆっくりしていきな
お前だち 伝ってくれるがい
WVVVV
ハァ バァ ハア...
がんば
ホレ 頑上央って
そうそう うまいじゃないか
ほんとに助かるよ
魔法で作っだんじゃ なにもならないからね
そこをくぐらせて そう 2回続けるの
おばあちゃん やっぱりの帰る
だって こうしてる間に
ハクが死んじゃうかもしれない
お父さんやお母さんが
食べられちゃうかもしれない
まあ もうちょっとお待ち
さあ 出来ちよ
かカみど
髪指めにお使い
わあ きれい...
お守りの...
つお
みんなで編いだ糸を
編みこんであるかがからね
ありがとう
いい時に来ちね
お客さんだよ 出ておくれ
ハイ
ああっ/
ハク/
ああ よかっだ
ケガがは? もう大丈夫なの?
よかっだ
フフフ グッドタイミングね
おばあちゃん ハク 生きてだ
ハ2韻
あなだのしただことは もうとがめません
その代わり その了をしっかり守るんだみよ
さあ坊やだち お帰りの時間だよ
まだ遊びにおいで
チュッ
お前はここにいな
あだしの手助けをしておくれ
ア... ア...
おばあちゃん/
ありがとう 私 行くね
大丈夫 あんだならやの遂げるよ
私の本当の名前は千尋っていうんです
ちひろ... いい名だね
自分の名前を大事にね
ハイ
さっ お行き
うん
おばあちゃん ありがとう さようなら
ハク 聞いて
お母さんから聞いただんで
自分では覚えてなかっだんだけど
私 小さい時 川に落ちちことがあるの
その川はもうマンションになって
埋められちゃっだんだって
でも 今 思い出しだの
その川の名は...
その川はね コバハ用
あなだの本当の名は
コハ2
ああーっ
千尋 ありがとう 私の本当の名は
ニギハヤミ コハクヌシだ
ニギハヤセミ?
ニギハヤミ コハクヌシ
すごい名前 神さまみだい
私も思い出した
千尋が私の中に落ちだ時のことを
クツを拾おうとしただんだよ
そう ゴリ ソンがを浅間に運んでくれたのね
うれしい...
帰って来ち/
坊は連れて戻って来だんだろうね
ヒッ/
バーバ
坊-- / ケガはなかっだかい
ひどい目にあっだねぇ うん?
坊 あなだ ひとりで立てるようになっだの?
エエ/
湯パーパさま 約束です
千尋と両親を人間の世界に戻して下さい
フン そう簡単じはいかないよ
世の中にはキマリというものがあるんだ
ブーッ
うるさいよ/
パーパのケチ もうやめなみよ
ヘっ...?
とても面白かっだよ 坊
で でもさ これはキマリなんだよ
じ ゃないと隊いが解けないんだよ
千を泣かしただら
パーバ キライになっちゃうかガらね
そ そんな...
おばあちゃん
おばあちゃん?
今 そっちへ行きます
おきて
控のことは ハクから聞きましだ
かくご
フン いい覚本だ
これはお前の契約書だよ こっちへおいで
坊 すぐ終わるからね
大丈夫よ
この中から お前の
お父さんとお母さんを見つけな
チャンスは一回だ
ビタダリと当てられだら お前だちちは自由だよ
ん? おばあちゃん だめ
ここにはお父さんもお母さんもいないもん
いない? それがお前の答えかい?
うん
ヒッ
大当だりーっ
ヨーシ / ヤッター
みんな ありがとう
行きな お前の勝ちだ
早く行っちまいな
お世話じなりましだ
フン
さようなら
ありがとう
まだねー
ハク
行こう/
お父さんとお母さんは?
先に行ってる
水がない/
私はこの先には行けない
千尋はもと求道をだどればいいんだ
でも 決してふり向いちぁいけないよ
トンネルを出るまではね
ハクは? ハクはどうするの?
私は湯パーパと話をつけて弟子をやめる
平気さ 本当の名を取り戻しだから
元の世界に私も戻るよ
まだ どこかがで会える?
ウン きっと
きっとよ
きっと さあ行きな ふのり向かないで
千尋ーっ
なにしてるの 早く来なさい
あ...
お母さん/ お父さん/
だめじゃない 急じいなくなっちゃ
行くよ
お母さん なんともないの?
ええ?
引っ越しのトラック
もう着いちぁゃってるわよ
千尋 早くおいで
あしもと
足元 気をつけな
千尋 そんなにくっつかないでよ
歩きしじくいわ
出口だよ
あれ?
なあに?
ひでぇ
ほこり
わぁ 中も換だらけだ
いただずら?
ガかなぁ?
だから やだって言っだのよ
オーライ オーライ 平気よ
千尋 行くよ
千尋 早くしなさい
ノ7がんでんる2 短のとどの移ぐ
ノビつるちかの編2 憂を尽をり
ノグ婦ん2み4 志?きがながんが
ノそのウツごこうでぎっと あみびさだど発える②
ノ上ク淡みあやえろの そのさび のとな
ノをを法/!識の 革さを嫌2
ノ固てん女ぐ 部級)て忌え2ゲカど
ノごの労連 ががを箇チ2
ノさみながらのとさきの 間みみ次
ノが7な2の2るをグ を82
ノ全ぎてりりる2大著 区ん選 <大著
ノ疹る破る巻ちる みんなみなびび
ノ7がんでんる2 短のとどの移ぐ
ノロつるが導でる 退を上どう
ノグのがんみのを 序 ぐみのみク
ノ己どくぐろの2で そっことうどみう
ノ2角てのりく級の そのみみのどのりつと
ノ/岳がださくの ささやきをを胡ぐ
ノご〇女ごだ表のがさ 細ののち
ノ新んりり時用びさがる
ノダひどばクの角2 のが座
ノが8なる2のク2 がをさてめケ
ん交の九の2が るうさがり
ノ凛ぐちの のつるごごだど
ノカのさんのながグのど 太フ72をのら